export const quiz =  {
  "quizTitle": "React Quiz Component Demo",
  "nrOfQuestions": "5",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How can you access the state of a component from inside of a member function?",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answerSelectionType": "single",
      "answers": [
        "this.getState()",
        "this.prototype.stateValue",
        "this.state",
        "this.values"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "3",
      "point": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "ReactJS is developed by _____?",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answerSelectionType": "single",
      "answers": [
        "Google Engineers",
        "Facebook Engineers"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2",
      "point": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "ReactJS is an MVC based framework?",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answerSelectionType": "single",
      "answers": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2",
      "point": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following concepts is/are key to ReactJS?",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answerSelectionType": "single",
      "answers": [
        "Component-oriented design",
        "Event delegation model",
        "Both of the above",
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "3",
      "point": "30"
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the advantages of React JS?",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answerSelectionType": "multiple",
      "answers": [
        "React can be used on client and as well as server side too",
        "Using React increases readability and makes maintainability easier. Component, Data patterns improves readability and thus makes it easier for manitaining larger apps",
        "React components have lifecycle events that fall into State/Property Updates",
        "React can be used with any other framework (Backbone.js, Angular.js) as it is only a view layer"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": [1, 2, 4],
      "point": "20"
    },
  ]
}

export const hindiQuiz = {
	"quizTitle": "React Quiz",
  "nrOfQuestions": "5",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "क्रिएट-रिएक्शन-ऐप इंस्टॉल करने के लिए निम्न में से किस कमांड का उपयोग किया जाता है?",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answerSelectionType": "single",
      "answers": [
        "npm install -g create-react-app",
        "npm install create-react-app",
        "npm install -f create-react-app",
        "install -g create-react-app"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "1",
      "point": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "ReactJS _____ द्वारा विकसित किया गया है?",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answerSelectionType": "single",
      "answers": [
        "गूगल इंजीनियर्स",
        "फेसबुक इंजीनियर"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "2",
      "point": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "क्या React.js मेमोरी में वर्चुअल डोम बनाता है?",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answerSelectionType": "single",
      "answers": [
        "सत्य",
        "असत्य"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "1",
      "point": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "निम्नलिखित में से कौन सी अवधारणा ReactJS की कुंजी है/हैं?",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answerSelectionType": "single",
      "answers": [
        "घटक-उन्मुख डिजाइन",
        "घटना प्रतिनिधिमंडल मॉडल",
        "ऊपर के दोनों",
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "3",
      "point": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "निम्नलिखित में से कौन सा इनबिल्ट हुक ऑफ रिएक्ट है?",
      "questionType": "text",
      "answerSelectionType": "multiple",
      "answers": [
        "useEffect()",
        "useRef()",
        "useCreate()",
        "useLayoutEffect()"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": [1, 2, 4],
      "point": "20"
    },
  ]
} 